This is how I'll become.
Supreme Commander!
A hero!
This is my story!
All
right.
The end of the day.
I was looking for a dream.
It's not long ago.
I was looking for a
dream. It's not long ago.
It's not long ago. It's not
long ago. I'd hoped to do.
But when you were here.
I was connected to myself.
I've been connected.
See you
next
time.
Hey isn't that a motto Peach uh-huh
you hadn't eaten one until after
we were separated right Can you blame
me the procedures and the paperwork
were a headache quite a few people
choose not to eat them it's just well
i had assumed your powers were a
direct result from eating the peaches
There is a connection between them.
In fact, the truth is, the peaches
are what caused us to look like this.
I want to hear the whole story!
It might be best if we
start with my story.
Are you sure?
It must be painful for you.
He needs to know the truth.
Besides, I can provide a much more elegant,
articulate account of what happened.
Miss Nahon.
I had a job in the human world.
As you may have guessed, I
worked in the modeling industry.
Uh, right.
Until one day, I was
involved in a motto mishap.
I hadn't eaten a peach.
Due to my love of beauty,
I thought I might develop
a rejuvenation ability
if I waited until after
I'd aged to eat one.
But I wasn't in a position to choose.
After I consumed it, the
peach's power went haywire.
When I awoke,
I had been carried to a dimly lit room,
and this creepy old woman was sitting
there, staring at me.
Noticing my confusion,
she explained everything.
This was the Onbeo Bureau, a research
facility dedicated to studying Shuki.
I couldn't process anything the
woman said to me after that.
A facility for studying Shuki?
Well, then what was I
What are I doing there?
No!
My beautiful body has been ruined!
These accidents do not
occur in the human world.
One theory is that they are
caused by Mato's miasma,
but more research is
required at this time.
We believe you are a valuable
subject for our study,
and we ask for your unwavering
cooperation in our experience.
Pe-experiments?
No way!
Cure me now!
Get me back, my beautiful body!
As our research progresses, we shall
find a method to cure you as well.
Until that time comes, please
do it for the good of humanity.
You have our deepest gratitude.
They poked and prodded me all over.
made me into a lab rat.
That's awful.
But there was a silver lining.
I became aware of my ability
to transverse through objects.
I waited for the right moment,
and I escaped with my friends.
Everyone else escaped through various
means, but all of our stories are the same.
When I saw all their scars, I was furious.
Were you with them, too?
Up till the part where I ate a
peach and Mato and it went haywire.
When I changed, the pain was excruciating.
I discovered this place and fought a battle
to hold on to my intellect for years.
When I had finally gotten things
under control, I met these guys.
That must have been horrible.
Now do you see why I had to rescue
you in such a convoluted way?
Mato has a gristly dark side.
Something so terrible.
We have to tell people! No point.
The Onmyo Bureau professes
that the existence
of Mato serves the
country's best interests.
They'll just use their abilities
and political clout to silence us.
Isn't it proof enough that you were left
completely in the dark until you met us?
Well...
That's why we have got
to be aggressive too!
We're gonna march into the
Onmyo Bureau and tear it down!
To save anyone who's facing
the same threat! Right?
Come here, boys!
Meet Kumadoji!
Akura.
The Unihorn.
Well, I prefer to call it Kidomaru.
These three beings possess a staggering
amount of strength, even for Shuuki.
Taming them wasn't exactly easy.
They learn their place once
you knock them around a little.
Right, Kuma?
We've readied our forces for battle.
And we've identified an invasion route.
We can attack any time we want.
Hold on a second.
I get how you feel and all,
but a plan like that would
hurt a lot of innocent people.
If the Defense Force knew what you just
told me, they would never let it slide!
If we ask for their help...
What makes you think
their Supreme Commander
isn't aware of the Omeo Bureau's actions?
If their policy involves making
us suffer on the country's behalf,
then they're our enemy! But wait!
Kyoka and the others!
Don't worry!
The three of us are perfectly capable of
finding a way to fix this mess ourselves!
Go tell everyone!
Do exactly as we planned earlier! Right!
Wait, what's happening?
It's time for a warm-up.
Oh my, we're in the middle of nowhere.
Yuki, where are you?
This way.
I've been here several times,
but I traveled by Ame no Mitori.
Commander, can you sense Yuki?
Well, it seems as though my legs
are carrying me towards those rocks.
They're in a cave, huh?
They must have hidden the entrance.
I suspect the humanoid Shuki that
kidnapped Yuki have made their home inside.
Tenka, we're heading in.
This feeling is the first for me.
Now I know exactly what it's like
to have my boyfriend stolen from me.
Once Shushu pries open the cave
entrance, we'll rush inside.
Saving Yuki is our number one priority.
Avoid combat whenever possible.
And if the humanoids try to interfere?
Follow the Supreme Commander's
orders and push for dialogue.
If they won't comply, combat is permitted.
Okay.
Then we should get going.
An ambush?
I got this!
Golden hour!
Three, five seconds!
Huh?
These half-pints, Shuuki,
are a waste of our time.
The hostage comes first.
Let's get moving!
So cool.
I better step up my... Whoa!
Everyone!
Give it up for Coco!
You must be my prey!
She blasted the cave
open! Get us! Feel that!
Sahara! What?
Take this!
We've got this covered! Thanks!
I won't let you get in
the commander's way!
You're dead meat!
So this is a Mato cave.
It's very different
from the caves monitored
by our recon teams at the heart of Mato.
It's small and cramped,
and there aren't any peaches who
are limited to my field of vision.
But should I try teleporting
us farther inside?
Hold it!
That weapon-wielding Shuki.
It's no joke.
The little slave must be just up ahead.
It looks like it.
Yuki is the priority.
Go on ahead without us.
Thanks, you two.
We'll meet you back here, Eisa.
Well, lucky you!
Battling alongside your brilliant sister.
This must be the thrill
of a lifetime, Himari.
It sure is.
It's death by asthma for these guys.
Before the commanders come
back here, let's wipe them out.
You stay here.
What are you...
Miss Kyoka!
I'm surprised you
already made it this far.
I bet your friends are
busy with Coco and...
Teleportation
I get the gist of your ability,
so that's how it's gonna be.
We should be safe here for the time being.
You alright, little slave?
Did they hurt you?
Oh, I'm fine!
How'd you manage to loc?
- I won't be able to move
until we get this over with!
Here goes Huh?
The price of her ability, this
must be how she tracked me down?
Miss Tenka
Why are you doing it too?
I'm rewarding him for
surviving all on his own
Sit still.
We need to finish this up quickly
and rendezvous with Himari.
The plan is to collect the others, and
then teleport back to the dorm as a group.
The others?
So they came all this way just to save me?
Wait a minute!
How long is this supposed to last?
I found you.
Hey, Kyo, you good?
I can move.
Sure!
Stand aside.
She's my big sister. What?
Yuki!
Stay out of this!
Please just hear me out for once!
I beg you!
Oh, Yuki.
I never could say no to you
when you gave me that look.
She's not trying to kill us?
His sister.
Do you think it's possible?
Let me explain.
I'll tell you the whole story.
Everything that happened to her.
Okay, but keep it brief.
Perfect!
All that's left is to set up the futon so
everyone can lie down as
soon as they get home.
I should clean the bathroom, too.
What else is there?
It's Nei's job to protect the
dorm, until Mr. Yuki's back! Coco!
Oh my god!
Sahara!
All you've done is run away from me!
Ain't you gonna fight?
I'll ask one last time!
Are you willing to negotiate?
Not a chance!
It's kill or be killed!
Okay then, I guess that settles it.
Paradigm shift!
Crazy shape!
About time you got serious.
Now let's see who's really the strongest.
There they are.
They just keep coming.
Without so much as a
glance, what did she do?
Himari!
You may have performed well
during the exhibition match,
but you're still a beginner.
Do yourself a favor and obey
your magnificent sister.
Then I'd be happy to provide you
with some sisterly protection.
Whatever.
The enemy is wide open. Hover bullet!
It's smarter than it looks.
Attacking blindly and
without understanding
her ability would be an ugly thing to do.
So instead, I'll...
The Onmyo Bureau?
Peach is backfiring.
Them studying all of the effects?
I knew about their Shuki research,
but to think, they're doing something
so inhumane behind the scenes.
If what you're claiming is true, then
we'll destroy the Bureau. Believe me.
And we'll continue to do as we
please, killing anyone in our way.
Does that mean you still plan on
using Shuki to start an uprising?
Well, what good would trusting
two cogs in the machine do?
A lot of people are going to suffer.
We're the victims too, you know.
Listen, I swear you can trust Miss Kyoka.
She's my commander.
But she treats you as if
you're some kind of slave,
forcing you to do her bidding.
That...
That was my decision.
I chose to become Miss Kyoka's
slave so that I can be a hero.
I have to help my friends.
Then we'll use all our strength to stop
you. Miss Kyoka! I'm sorry. She's right.
The Demon Defense Force would
do the same thing. Come on!
Pixie!
The battle is about to begin.
Stay out of the way.
She cares about her little brother.
This is one opponent Yuki can't fight.
It would behoove him to not get involved.
Now then, shall we get started?
It's the Unihorn.
That one is all yours.
As it should be!
So you're my opponent.
Interesting. Oh, that's right.
I forgot to introduce myself.
I'm Tenka, commander of the Sixth
Squadron and Yuki's girlfriend.
I'm your future sister-in-law.
It's a pleasure.
I'll kill you!
I can't stop them.
Damn it, this is bad!
Mmh!
Go with me!
He's fast and strong, huh?
What's the matter, princess?
What? Yeah!
Come and get me!
Your attacks are sloppy and excessive!
So that's my best shot!
Come on!
Gotcha!
I'll crush you into itty bitty pieces!
What the hell?
This thing is tougher than steel!
Well in that case, bam!
Followed by...
Boom!
Huh?
There's not a single scratch on it!
It's no use.
Kuma's invincible.
And I'm slimy.
Hitting us ain't gonna work.
Which means we're the worst opponents
that you two could ever ask for!
This one's mine!
Golden Hour!
Freeze five seconds!
You were pretty good with that spear.
Now say goodbye.
Just a little parting gift.
Uh-huh.
Uh-huh. Uh-huh. T-Mari!
T-Mari!
Hmm?
Uh-huh.
Shikoku. Huh?
I found what we were looking for.
Oh. Wonderful.
Nice job hunting them down.
They're in combat with
the demon defense force.
The demon defense force!
It might be time to start
introducing ourselves as gods.
Hark, humans and behold
her holiness has arrived.
Well, how did that sound?
Entirely devoid of dignity, really I!
Will make us look divine
when we get there?
Good plan
Well, shall we go?
Thank you.
I don't want to go back.
and I'm moving objects.
Oh crap, our cover's blood!
Next time, death badge, Owl the Excite!
You pink, Demon Defense Force!